

FILIP LIZOŃ

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

GET IN CONTACT

+48 600 113 271

 \searrow

filip.lizon1@gmail.com

FIND ME



github.com/filiplizon



<u>linkedin.com/in/filip-lizon</u>



leezon.gatsbyjs.io

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a 25-year-old computer science engineer with nearly two years of experience as a Frontend Developer. I love creating websites and web applications and find immense satisfaction in doing so. I am ambitious, consistent, a quick learner, and always eager to learn new technologies. I believe that my contribution to your company would be valuable, and working with you would enable me to have a faster professional development.

SKILLS

- · JavaScript, TypeScript
- · React, Next, Gatsby
- · Redux, Recoil
- HTML
- CSS, SCSS, CSS-in-JS
- TailwindCSS
- · Theme UI, Chakra UI, antd
- REST API
- i18n
- Cypress

TOOLS

- GIT
- · Github / Bitbucket
- npm/yarn
- JIRA
- · Adobe XD / Adobe PS / Figma

OTHER SKILLS

- Problem solving
- Teamwork
- Analytical thinking
- · Information search
- · Attention to details

EXPERIENCE

12.2022 - 03.2023 | Junior Frontend Developer | Chimera Prime

- Designing, implementing, and testing code based on business and technical requirements of a recruitment process supporting application
- Creating responsive user interfaces using TypeScript / React / Chakra UI
- Integrating user interface with APIs using standard network protocols
- Troubleshooting and debugging code, as well as optimizing application performance.
- Working with Git version control system to manage code and implement changes
- Keeping up-to-date knowledge of the latest trends and technologies in the field of front-end development

06.2021 - 11.2022 | Frontend Developer | NEONET

- Preparing landing pages in Magento 2
- Creating responsive landing pages (HTML, CSS, JavaScript) based on graphic designs created in Adobe XD, Adobe PS or Figma
- Development and testing of the functionality of the online store
- Troubleshooting application issues and proposing new solutions
- · Creating mailings in HTML

EDUCATION

10.2017 - 03.2022

WYŻSZA SZKOŁA INFORMATYKI I ZARZĄDZANIA "COPERNICUS" Bachelor of engineering, Computer Science

INTERESTS

- · Travelling
- Working out at the gym
- Investing
- Football
- History

LANGUAGES

- polish native
- english b2